<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Forgetful</string>

    <string name="overview_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="overview_body_text">
        Going through the trouble of leaving your house and having to
        come back because you forgot your wallet or phone is something everybody has gone though and
        won\'t stop going through. This app is designed to help you leave those troubles behind
        instead with 5 key tips to keep you from leaving your place without everything that you
        need.\n\n
        Swipe right or click on a tab to learn more!
    </string>

    <!--Routine Fragment-->
    <string name="routine_title">Make a routine</string>
    <string name="routine_tip_text">
        Having a routine helps people remember more easily by making
        something a habit. By making your own routine, whether it\'s patting all of your pockets
        before walking out of that door or singing a song to remind you of what you need before
        leaving, you will be less likely to leave for the outside world unprepared.
    </string>

    <!--Plop Fragment-->
    <string name="plop_title">Designate a \'plop area\'</string>
    <string name="plop_tip_text">
        The next step is to have what I like to call a \'plop area\', any place or container that
        you drop your stuff in at. This reduces the chance that you\'ll leave your items in an
        unusual place and the chance that you\'ll panic when you think you\'ve lost something. As
        well, you\'ll be less likely to forget to bring something with you if you ever forget to go
        through your routine because all of your stuff will be right there for you. How convenient!
    </string>

    <!-- Jot Fragment -->
    <string name="jot_title">Jot it down</string>
    <string name="jot_tip_text">
        A human can forget, but a piece of paper can\'t. Having something as archaic as a list on
        paper will increase the likelihood of you walking through that door with everything that
        you need. A simple yet effective tool!
    </string>

    <!--Reminders Fragment-->
    <string name="reminders_title">Set reminders</string>
    <string name="reminders_tip_text">
        If you ever forget to make sure you have the phone, wallet, keys, etc., having a
        reminder will keep you in check. Setting an alarm for any time before you leave can help
        remind you to make sure you have everything in your pockets. Just make sure to set a
        separate alarm from waking up to remind you that your alarm is nagging you for another
        important reason!
    </string>

    <!--PostIt Fragment-->
    <string name="postit_title">Post It!</string>
    <string name="postit_tip_text">
        This tip goes hand in hand with tip 3. If you\'re a person that relies on visuals, post-its
        are a must for you. Having post-its on your bathroom mirror is a great way to jog that
        memory while you\'re brushing those pearly whites, and even a post it on your door can keep
        you from rushing out without the keys to your car. Make sure not to go overboard with these
        as guests can call you in for an intervention if you stick post-its around your place saying
        \"DON\'T FORGET KEYS…\". I\'ll let you decide what\'s overboard and what\'s not.
    </string>
</resources>

